[
  {
    "question": "1/2",
    "answer": "half",
    "tasks": ["half"]
  },
  {
    "question": "1/3",
    "answer": "one thirds",
    "tasks": ["one", "thirds"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3/4",
    "answer": "three quarters",
    "tasks": ["three", "quarters"]
  },
  {
    "question": "5/2",
    "answer": "five halves",
    "tasks": ["five", "halves"]
  },
  {
    "question": "8/9",
    "answer": "eight ninths",
    "tasks": ["eight", "ninths"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3/5",
    "answer": "three fifths",
    "tasks": ["three", "fifths"]
  },
  {
    "question": "12.17",
    "answer": "twelve point seventeen",
    "tasks": ["twelve", "point", "seventeen"]
  },
  {
    "question": "28.56",
    "answer": "twenty-eight point fifty-six",
    "tasks": ["twenty-eight", "point", "fifty-six"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3.9",
    "answer": "three point nine",
    "tasks": ["three", "point", "nine"]
  },
  {
    "question": "75%",
    "answer": "seventy-five percent",
    "tasks": ["seventy-five", "percent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "93%",
    "answer": "ninety-three percent",
    "tasks": ["ninety-three", "percent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "38%",
    "answer": "thirty-eight percent",
    "tasks": ["thirty-eight", "percent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 500 950",
    "answer": "three million five hundred thousand nine hundred and fifty",
    "tasks": ["three", "million", "five", "hundred", "thousand", "nine", "hundred", "and", "fifty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 934 379",
    "answer": "eight million nine hundred thirty-four thousand three hundred and seventy-nine",
    "tasks": [
      "eight",
      "million",
      "nine",
      "hundred",
      "thirty-four",
      "thousand",
      "three",
      "hundred",
      "and",
      "seventy-nine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 600 000",
    "answer": "one million six hundred thousand",
    "tasks": ["one", "million", "six", "hundred", "thousand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 900 300",
    "answer": "ten million nine hundred thousand three hundred",
    "tasks": ["ten", "million", "nine", "hundred", "thousand", "three", "hundred"]
  },
  {
    "question": "25 324",
    "answer": "twenty-five thousand three hundred and twenty-four",
    "tasks": ["twenty-five", "thousand", "three", "hundred", "and", "twenty-four"]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 893",
    "answer": "thirteen thousand eight hundred and ninety-three",
    "tasks": ["thirteen", "thousand", "eight", "hundred", "and", "ninety-three"]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 534",
    "answer": "seven thousand five hundred and thirty-four",
    "tasks": ["seven", "thousand", "five", "hundred", "and", "thirty-four"]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 600",
    "answer": "nine thousand six hundred",
    "tasks": ["nine", "thousand", "six", "hundred"]
  },
  {
    "question": "836",
    "answer": "eight hundred and thirty-six",
    "tasks": ["eight", "hundred", "and", "thirty-six"]
  },
  {
    "question": "396",
    "answer": "three hundred and ninety-six",
    "tasks": ["three", "hundred", "and", "ninety-six"]
  },
  {
    "question": "25 апреля",
    "answer": "the twenty-fifth of April",
    "tasks": ["the", "twenty-fifth", "of", "April"]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 ноября",
    "answer": "the thirteenth of November",
    "tasks": ["the", "thirteenth", "of", "November"]
  },
  {
    "question": "31 января",
    "answer": "the thirty-first of January",
    "tasks": ["the", "thirty-first", "of", "January"]
  },
  {
    "question": "1ый",
    "answer": "first",
    "tasks": ["first"]
  },
  {
    "question": "2ой",
    "answer": "second",
    "tasks": ["second"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3ий",
    "answer": "third",
    "tasks": ["third"]
  },
  {
    "question": "4ий",
    "answer": "fourth",
    "tasks": ["fourth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "5ый",
    "answer": "fifth",
    "tasks": ["fifth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "6ый",
    "answer": "sixth",
    "tasks": ["sixth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "8ый",
    "answer": "eighth",
    "tasks": ["eighth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "9ый",
    "answer": "ninth",
    "tasks": ["ninth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "21ый",
    "answer": "twenty first",
    "tasks": ["twenty", "first"]
  },
  {
    "question": "32ой",
    "answer": "thirty second",
    "tasks": ["thirty", "second"]
  },
  {
    "question": "43ий",
    "answer": "forty third",
    "tasks": ["forty", "third"]
  },
  {
    "question": "55ый",
    "answer": "fifty fifth",
    "tasks": ["fifty", "fifth"]
  }
]
